<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Twissel Hacking Projects</title>
    <link>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Twissel Hacking Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 20:21:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>In love with my first 3D Printer!</title>
      <link>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/in-love-with-my-first-3d-printer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 20:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/in-love-with-my-first-3d-printer/</guid>
      <description>I was a bit skeptical and fearful that I&#39;d buy something that would beat me, and then I&#39;d have to confess to my friends that I failed. And that&#39;s why it took me sooo long to buy a 3D printer. Now they are cheap. Like 200usd cheap. And getting cheaper and easier to build every fucking day.  So I read tutorials, blogs, youtube videos. The best the worst the ugly of chinese DIY kits and what&#39;s the best start a noob can have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Game Development in C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/starting-game-development-in-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 01:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/starting-game-development-in-c/</guid>
      <description>After many failed little pet projects I finally started to work on a simple game. Tired of the failures of half-assed abstractions and poorly supported cross-platform languages I decided I could just learn C++.  I must say that after 3 months I&#39;m really happy on the progress I&#39;ve so far. Tooling So far, I&#39;ve been bootstrapping a simple map editor with SFML (Graphics, Sound libraries). And imgui (For the Map Editor and debugging tools).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poor Man&#39;s Web Automation Using Chrome Extensions</title>
      <link>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/poor-man-s-web-automation-using-chrome-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 21:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/poor-man-s-web-automation-using-chrome-extensions/</guid>
      <description>So let&#39;s say you are trying to integrate with one of those third parties which their entire business relies on making it hard for you to access the information they publish. For example, let&#39;s say you are trying to keep a database of interesting public profiles from LinkedIn, and you are interested only in a couple of indicators from each profile. How can we automate the gathering of this information?  One possibility would be to use something like Mechanize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Text Classification with Python&#39;s NLTK</title>
      <link>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/simple-text-classification-with-python-s-nltk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 21:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/simple-text-classification-with-python-s-nltk/</guid>
      <description>Last Tuesday I had a very interesting talk with the CTO&#39;s and Engineering leads of the SocialAtom Ventures. The idea was to talk about the current challenges everybody is facing and share the experiences we&#39;ve had with similar problems. One of the companies (Bankity) is struggling to separate bogus messages from their transaction messages. This is currently being done through Google&#39;s Prediction API which not only makes them dependent on a vendor, but also is a black-box that is hard to reason about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring for Drones</title>
      <link>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/monitoring-for-drones/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 01:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/monitoring-for-drones/</guid>
      <description>Some days ago I met the people from Göra Makerspace. Among many interesting projects that mix Art and Engineering these guys are trying to build their own Auto-Pilot System inspired by ArduPilot.  There&#39;s still a lot of work to be done but they asked me about ways to record and chart their sensor data in order to be able to fine-tune all the rocket-science math behind autonomous flight. Reinventing The Wheel Currently the team developed their own protocol for metrics which is using bluetooth for transmission of the stat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Kingdom for a Good GameDev Stack</title>
      <link>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/my-kingdom-for-a-good-gamedev-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 20:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/my-kingdom-for-a-good-gamedev-stack/</guid>
      <description>I really just wanted an easy-to-use 2d game engine for multi-platform (mobile) development. But then this happened. An Open Source Replacement for Unity, or Why Volunteering to Walk to Mordor? Saying &#34;I have used Unity&#34; is a sad way to start explaining why I decided to check the status of the open source game engines and media libraries.  Basically my experience with Unity was a good reminder of why I love OpenSource.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Week of Arduino Fun</title>
      <link>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/first-week-of-arduino-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 15:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/first-week-of-arduino-fun/</guid>
      <description>So I remember my love for Electronics when I started my university.  The problem of hardware is having stupid and idiotic hands. Burning stuff. Buying things... or is that actually the fun? :D  Things have changed a lot from my PIC programming lessons in my Uni. Lot of Amateur friendly hardware is out there, and is not only cheap. Is rather modular!  So I got a simple kit to remember even the polarity of a LED.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Starting a Blog? Why Getting Away?</title>
      <link>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/why-starting-a-blog-why-getting-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 15:04:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://twissel.narcosoft.com/post/why-starting-a-blog-why-getting-away/</guid>
      <description>Hello.  My name is Diego. And I started studying computer science with high idealistic goals in my head. Creating robots, making true AI, cure hunger, destroy inequality. Create UTOPIA  Then, working after a long time in what could be the most fun projects you see machines prevalence in the modern world has not been what we expected. We have created what many of the sci-fi writers warned us about automation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>